704.929.3399 joshguion@icloud.com 1055 B Eastover Drive, Mount Pleasant SC 29464

Profile

With 10+ years of customer service experience, I have developed a strong passion for creating and maintaining personal relationships with clients. With a recent career change into Web Development, I am excited to combine this experience with my newfound passion for developing beautiful, user-friendly websites and applications.

Skills

HTML5 | CSS3 | SASS | JavaScript | AngularJS | Phaser | Git | GitHub | Node Package Manager | Bower | Underscore | Bootstrap.

Education

The Iron Yard, Charleston - Front-End Engineering, October 2015 - January 2016

South Piedmont Community College - Certified Nursing Assistant, August 2009 - December 2009

Experience

FAMILY ROOM SPECIALIST, APPLE INC; NASHVILLE, TN & CHARLESTON, SC – SEPTEMBER 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2015

Provided customer support with multiple technical issues in various Apple products. Specialized in resolving customer conflicts and issues relating to product support and provided personal training for our customers.

BARISTA, STARBUCKS; NASHVILLE, TN - JULY 2012 - JUNE 2013

Provided prompt, courteous, and reliable service with a customer-focused attitude. Performed cash handling and cash register functions in an accurate and consistent manner. Maintained a calm presence during periods of high volume. Anticipated customer and store needs by constantly evaluating the work environment.

CNA, COMPASSIONATE CARE OF CHARLOTTE; CHARLOTTE, NC – OCTOBER 2009 - MAY 2011

Commended for chart accuracy, effective team collaboration, patient relations, and consistent delivery of empathetic care. Preserved patient dignity and minimized discomfort while carrying out duties such as bedpan changes, diapering, emptying drainage bags, and bathing.